A pixel art level? This is getting
ridiculous.
>> How am I supposed to use eight-bit
powers? Yeah, you're having trouble
figuring out any of your powers.
Change of subject. What's going on with
this level?
>> Oh, Jimmy really sucks at gardening.
It's rotten. This is the work of the
shroud. But it's something different,
something new. Look at the little pixel
guy. Something's got him spooked.
Oh my god. Are those swarms? What's
wrong with them? Usually they're so
sweet and cuddly. Yeah, they look extra
bitey.
>> It must be that rot. They're like zombie
swarms. Oh wait, swombies. Oh, that's
good. Yeah, swombies. They're called
swombies now. Swombies, huh? Don't
forget that's mine. Cute and terrifying.
They're coming. Run!
[Music]
Maybe we don't have to run, but we
should still get out of here. Invaders
must kill.
Plant zombie. Some plant plant be back.
I've nothing for that.
Ew, did his arm just come off?
[Music]
I get it. It's bad timing, but this
reminds me we have not had lunch. Uh-oh,
here he comes again.
He's unconscious. Give him a little
orange juice. Sometimes that helps.
Maybe we can try putting him in the
fusion chamber. Yeah, that makes way
more sense. Gorilla, take care of the
zombies.
>> Swombies. Swombies. Just feels good to
say. While me and Banana get Weed Man
into the hybrid pod thingy. Oh great,
yeah. Fighting an undead army, the easy
job.
>> And I'll grab his bits and pieces. Wait
a sec.
Oh man, this won't be easy with those
cute little voices.
Sorry. Sorry.
Why are you doing this? I know you like
your lasers.
[Music]
Gorilla. Coming. I did my best, guys,
but the swombies are still swarming.
>> Yeah, it doesn't work when you do it.
Hurry up and get that thing going. Dang
it, no pandemonium particles. What do we
do now?
>> Banana, we saw you pick some up on the
last level.
>> You're hiding the peepee in your pants.
Fine. Man, I was going to use these to
make some cool powers for myself.
Someday. Someday.
I am the creator of life. I wonder if
I'll know when to stop. Will I make
something one day even I won't
understand?
Banana, hurry. Hey, I'm going as fast as
I can. I'm trying to do a really good
job, so there's no notes.
Ah, thank you, my friends. You saved us.
You're welcome.
[Music]
These new tentacles give me the power to
heal. As a thanks, I will give you the
power as well.
>> great, another power he won't be able to
figure out.
>> Shut up. Thank you. We will stay behind
and heal our friends. If you find the
source of the rot, I believe you will
find what you're looking for. Sounds
like this Jimmy fetch quest just got a
side mission. Side mission? They're just
a waste of time. Nobody likes side
missions.
>> No one likes you. Ah, come to me, my
swombies.
>> That's my joke.
>> I will heal you. That kind of tickles.
That's real biting. Stop biting. Stop
biting.